<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Audiobook on Siddhartha Golu</title>
    <link>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/tags/audiobook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Audiobook on Siddhartha Golu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:49:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.siddharthagolu.com/tags/audiobook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Empire of Pain: The Secret History of the Sackler Dynasty</title>
      <link>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/empire-of-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 08:49:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/empire-of-pain/</guid>
      <description>If you want to understand how the opioid crisis began, read this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I Talk About When I Talk About Running by Haruki Murakami</title>
      <link>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/running-murakami/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 20:09:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/running-murakami/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/4168404043&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.siddharthagolu.com/images/running-murakami.jpg#center&#34; alt=&#34;Running Cover&#34; title=&#34;Running Cover&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pain is inevitable, suffering is optional.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have no affinity for running, even for short jogs, and much less for wanting to run long distances. Although this is not because I hate exercises - one of those rare things that I figured out early in life was my desire to remain healthy as long as possible and that of course means I need to keep myself fit - but probably my distaste for running stems from the monotonous nature of the activity. You keep pounding your legs with a short breath and no rest in sight, what is there to&#xA;enjoy and look forward to?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Blood by John Carreyrou</title>
      <link>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/bad-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 23:39:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/bad-blood/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/2635590846&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.siddharthagolu.com/images/bad_blood.webp#center&#34; alt=&#34;Bad Blood Cover&#34; title=&#34;Bad Blood Cover&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-fool-the-world-and-become-a-billionaire&#34;&gt;How to fool the world and become a Billionaire&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I remember hearing about &lt;em&gt;Elizabeth Holmes&lt;/em&gt; when I was in my late teens, at that impressionable age when you get hyper-inspired by reading about icons that are going to change the world. There was a profile of her in Wired, with an eye-catching image of her wearing a turtleneck black sweater holding what looked like a test-tube with a tiny amount of blood with a science-y background. I remember it had made quite a distinct impression on my mind, no doubt helped by the fact that the profile had described her as &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;this Stanford dropout 20-something who was hailed as being a younger version of Einstein, was going to change the world&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Listen to and Understand Great Music by Robert Greenberg</title>
      <link>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/great-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:05:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.siddharthagolu.com/posts/reading/great-music/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/3030817409&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been a lover of music since my early childhood - runs in the family - and have imitated and performed songs (mostly inside my own head) on numerous occasions. Despite this lifelong love affair with music of all kinds, there was one particular genre of music that always baffled me. Mostly because of my own ignorance, but partially also because nobody else was talking about it. Nobody else in my own vicinity that is. It didn&amp;rsquo;t play on the radio, you won&amp;rsquo;t hear it playing on any of the countless music channels and certainly, nobody was going on tours giving live performances.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
