<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fiction on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fiction on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:53:52 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Midnight&#39;s Children by Salman Rushdie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/midnight-rushdie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:53:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/midnight-rushdie/</guid>
      <description>A phenomenally written book!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shame by Salman Rushdie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/shame-rushdie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 22:55:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/shame-rushdie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/4138625648&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/shame.jpg#center&#34; alt=&#34;Shame Cover&#34; title=&#34;Shame Cover&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve moved away from reading fiction, I find that I face a lot of inertia to pick up something purely for pleasure. Maybe this is a nasty by-product of wanting to be as &amp;ldquo;productive&amp;rdquo; as possible. But the more I have drifted away from reading for pleasure, more mechanical the whole process has become for me. Partly to avoid this feeling, and partly because of my shame at seeing my bookshelf filled with dusty unread books, I picked up this one to assuage my feelings of guilt.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stoner by John Williams</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/stoner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 19:45:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/stoner/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/1389128822&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Reading fiction has always been a double-edged sword for me. Some of the most intimate moments I&amp;rsquo;ve spent alone is while reading fictional stories, while at the same time, feeling a pang of disappointment for myself because I wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing anything &amp;ldquo;productive.&amp;rdquo; Is this mere entertainment? Am I just escaping my real-life responsibilities and reading stories of make-believe? While I still haven&amp;rsquo;t found sincere answers to these questions, I&amp;rsquo;ve grown more confident of what I enjoy and what I don&amp;rsquo;t, which has consequently helped me find peace with this conflict. Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that reading good literature is therapeutic for me - not to be used as an afterthought but essential to keep me functional.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Course of Love by Alain de Botton</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/the-course-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 20:21:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reading/the-course-of-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/review/show/1855122398&#34;&gt;Check it out on Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The School of Life - a massively popular YouTube channel - used to be this source of solace in some turbulent times of my college life.&#xA;It is not something that you&amp;rsquo;d think would be cheerful and uplifting - a quick glance at some of the most popular videos of the channel would include titles such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WRaaqN2Atxw&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Why we go cold on our partners&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zuKV2DI9-Jg&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Why you will marry the wrong person&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt; etc.&#xA;The honest yet straightforward mannger in which the narrator calmly tells us that even though it might feel like this is the worst possible time of your life, it is not usually so - it was a comforting thought - to feel and accept that things are fucked up and move on with quiet resignation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
